Long live Bata Bhai!
- Kids!
- Long live Bata Bhai!
You've been sitting here
for quite a while now.
Swami Bata Bhai salutes you.
So, what's today's chapter?
Disease.
I understand
what you guys are trying to ask.
Till now, we've seen plenty of diseases
that our white-coat doctor buddies
have cured.
But there's one disease
for which we've never found a cure.
And that disease is greed.
Hey, buddy!
Why are you making us rack our brains?
Everyone's come here
to watch Dhamaal and have some fun.
Once they watch Dhamaal,
they'll learn everything there is
to know about greed.
Kids, let me tell you something.
This story is also about
some greedy people,
and it began a hundred years ago.
On a dark, stormy night,
right in the middle of the sea,
a sea pirate named Shaitaan Singh,
in one massive action sequence,
beat up and killed dozens of Englishmen.
And then, he looted the treasure
of those greedy Englishmen.
He hid the treasure on an island
and drew up a map to it.
The Englishmen managed
to kill Shaitaan Singh,
but they never found that map.
Since then, to this day,
the map to that treasure
has been searched for
by all kinds of greedy crooks
and cheaters.
Jheenga…
I can't see anything.
Boss, remove the lid.
The lid.
He's such a dimwit.
I still can't see anything, Jheenga.
Hey, dumbo!
I mean the lid.
Remove the binocular's lid.
The lid.
Yes, now see.
- Leave me.
- Come on. We won't leave you.
We will break your bones now.
Finally, you're found.
Now, tell me where the treasure map is?
I won't tell you.
Search him.
Boss, he has a gun.
If he has a gun,
he must have the map, too.
Check again. Come on.
- Boss!
- What?
Your girlfriend Shabnam's photo
is in his wallet.
Shabbo?!
My Shabbo's photo…
How did you get it?
Hey!
Who else has
my Shabbo's photo?
Tell me, who else has it?
Who has her photo?
Who else has my Shabbo…
I will deal with you all later.
Prithvi!
I won't spare you now.
Boss!
Snatch away the map first
and then kill him.
- Yeah.
- Hey, search him.
Hey…
- Come here.
- Leave me.
Check properly.
- Boss, here's the map.
- Hey…
Boss, presenting to you
the treasure map.
Hey, found it.
Found the treasure map…
Hey, I've found the treasure map.
- Return that map.
- Hey! Back off!
To get this map, my heart was…
Fire! Fire!
Yes, my heart was burning
with a fire no one could put out.
Idiot! Is he mentally unstable?
Since birth!
Boss, we need to put out this fire.
And who are you to put out my fire?
No one can extinguish this fire…
Fire!
My map got burnt because of you.
I won't spare you.
Hey, half-brain!
You can't kill me.
Because the map
is stored in my memory.
And I won't… share it with you.
Then I will also…
torture you.
Did you feel the pain?
Yes, sir.
There comes my friend.
There goes your friend.
Fire!
He shouldn't be spared.
Don't leave him.
Kill him.
Yes!
Hey, blind fellow, aim with this eye.
Where's he?
I knew you would come to rescue me.
I didn't come here to rescue you.
I came to punish you.
Idiot, I gave you the map to decode,
but your greed got the better of you,
and you double-crossed me and ran away?
But bro,
I'm the one who called you here.
You called me
because you sensed danger.
Don't touch my family jewel.
Where's the map?
It got burned.
- What?!
- Don't worry.
The whole map is stored in my memory.
I will share every detail with you.
But first, find a way
to get us out of here, bro.
I'm begging you. Please,
get me out of this place safely.
- Boss.
- Yes.
He's there.
Hey, catch them.
- Hey.
- Catch them.
Make sure they don't run away.
Leave me.
Hey!
Nobody interferes.
He's my prey.
Okay, boss.
I'll blow up your head with my gun.
Leave him.
Boss! Careful!
Remember what your boss said?
Nobody interferes.
I'm the boss.
I cancel my own order.
Beat him up.
Hit him!
Leave… leave me.
Leave me. Leave me.
- Hey, blow air.
- Where?
In my eyes!
I'm doing it.
Take out your knife, come on.
Come on, aim.
Aim at him.
Aim for his chest.
Jheenga!
- Jheenga!
- Yes.
- Look at that pink pigeon.
- Where?
You tricked me.
Eyepatch!
- Now, have fun.
- Coconut.
Boss, pull it out.
Yes, I will.
I can't stand the sight of blood.
Wait a second.
It's out!
Hold me.
What a relief!
- Bye!
- Hey!
Cannon. Cannon.
Stop limping and run.
Hey, idiot!
Load it into the cannon.
- Light it!
- What to light?
Light the fuse.
Sorry, Guddu!
- Yes, turn it to the center. Center.
- Hit him.
Left… left! Fire!
Make sure to blow him into pieces.
Boss, the cannonball is going upward.
Boss, it's coming back down.
It's hot.
This will explode. We will die.
A cannonball…
It's missing.
Who's missing?
The "H" is missing.
Oh. Sorry, bro.
Here comes the "H".
Not there.
Place it after "D".
Sorry again.
I'll fix it right away.
Here comes the "H".
Bro. Sorry to inform you
that you're no longer alive.
Rest in peace.
Put that to your ear?
You've already slapped me.
Still, if you insist…
I told you to put this to your ear,
the stethoscope.
That's not necessary.
I have good news for you.
You're alive.
No. I want Prithvi.
I want the secret of the treasure.
Until then,
there's no good news for me.
No, listen. I've sent Mannu Makoda
to Prithvi's house at Chamboli Ghat.
He will come there to meet his girlfriend,
and we will grab him there.
- I want Prithvi.
- Bro, blood pressure…
- Your blood pressure…
- I want Prithvi.
- Bro. Your blood pressure is shooting up.
Bro, I'm such an amazing doctor.
It's getting under control now.
Oh… here comes his ICU.
Guddu!
What happened to you?
The same thing that happens every
time I see you.
After seeing you,
I can't notice anything else at all.
Okay, listen.
I've already spoken with the kids.
Come and meet them in the evening.
If the kids like you,
then our family will be complete.
If I've already won the mother,
then the kids are…
What?
I'll win them, too.
Hey, Lord Krishna!
Goddess Radha!
Always have Your blessings on me.
DONATION BOX
God,
You already know that I'm not
the greedy type of person.
Anyway, what more do I even want?
What do I want?
Just a beautiful girl,
whose father owns
an extra-large bungalow,
an extra-large car,
an extra-large bank balance.
And after marriage,
all of that should simply become mine!
That's all I want.
And for that,
I'll offer five lakh rupees as
a donation to You, God.
And yes, I've even brought
an advance payment.
Fifty whole rupees from me.
You'll definitely remember me for this!
God!
You've accepted
the request so quickly!
Do You have a 5G network?
You took my "extra-large" request
quite seriously.
It's an extra-large car.
Well, I can adjust to that much.
But God, You should also adjust a little.
I'll pay this 50 rupees along
with the full and final payment.
Why are you getting so angry, God?
Seth, when are you getting
your daughter Paro married?
Seth ji, every father worries
about his daughter's marriage.
I'm worried too.
With God's grace,
she will get married very soon.
Thank you for dropping me
off at the temple, Uncle.
- Bye, Dad.
- Bless you, dear.
Go safely.
Sorry. I hope you aren't hurt.
Not really.
But this heart did feel something.
What…
what's going on?
Now, I'm hurt.
But it's the sweet feeling.
Natthu.
Hey, Natthu.
- Did you notice?
- Yes.
I've enticed Seth's daughter.
No, Lallan, he's Seth.
But he's the d…
No need to be afraid of anyone.
When one has fallen in love,
then why fear?
And take this.
Distribute it to the poor on my behalf.
You also take some.
But…
money?
We were so happy on our wedding day.
I love you, Rosy.
Thank you for coming back into my life.
Thank you.
Adi, I will also play cricket.
Cricket?
You already took my wicket a year ago.
My Rosy left me.
I've been living like a widow
for the past year.
It's called a widower.
Be it a widower or a widow.
How does it matter?
No worries.
Do you remember
what you did on my wedding night?
Do you?
Flashback will be here and not there.
Sorry.
Surprise!
What are you doing here?
I was hiding below the bed.
To surprise bhabhi.
Is this how you should surprise…
Couldn't you come in the morning?
Adi, you're not so smart.
One can't declare
the surprise beforehand.
- Fire! Fire!
- Take this…
Fire! Fire!
Adi, please put out this fire.
I'm trying.
Manav, bring water. Quick.
Water! Water!
- Adi, please do something.
- Yes, I'm doing it.
Adi, water.
Throw water on bhabhi.
Manav, throw water quickly.
What have you done?
You told me to throw water.
Should you have thrown it on her face?
Look at her now.
She left that day.
And never returned.
Adi, I am not so smart.
I know.
- Stop crying and listen carefully.
- Okay.
I've told Rosy that my leg is fractured.
She's coming to see me.
I will make her so emotional
that she will never leave me again.
Adi, you're so smart.
I know.
Rogue! What did you say?
You don't keep change?
- Bhabhi is here. Bhabhi is here.
- Yes.
- Bhabhi…
- You don't have the change, do you?
Why don't you keep any change?
- Sorry, madam.
- Get lost! I don't want your "sorry".
She's such a dangerous woman.
- Let's go, Manav.
- Yes.
Sit there and enjoy the walnut.
Just don't do anything.
Okay.
Enough. Stop crying.
How did this happen?
I was lost in your memories
while boarding a bus.
Didn't realize when the bus crushed me.
Since then, I've been in bed.
All alone.
Lonely.
Helpless.
- Don't leave me alone, Rosy.
- Enough.
I've come back, right?
Now I will stay here with you.
Thank you. Thank you, Rosy.
Alright! It's okay.
Stupid!
Keep that weight down.
Okay.
Oh no!
Manav, what have you done?
I was trying to break the walnut.
But you've hurt your bhabhi instead.
I'm not so smart.
Manav, you idiot!
Bhabhi!
- Manav…
- Give this to me.
Walnut! Walnut!
Manav!
- Leave it!
- This walnut.
My walnut!
Adi, it fell.
It fell?! She fell!
No, I mean the walnut fell.
To hell with your walnut.
Pull your bhabhi up. Come on.
Yes! Yes!
Bhabhi, don't worry.
Be happy!
- Adi! Adi, what should I do?
- Pull up.
Down! Down!
Oh no!
Bhabhi. Don't worry.
What are you doing?
Are you pulling water from the well?
- Pull your bhabhi up. Come on.
- Manav!
Bhabhi, don't worry.
Oh no. Bhabhi!
- Bhabhi! Bhabhi!
- Pull me up.
- Don't worry.
- What are you doing?
Hey, you!
Keep it up, bhabhi.
Yes. Very good.
- Bhabhi! Are you alright, bhabhi?
- Are you fine?
- Are you alright?
How are you standing on your feet?
It's a miracle!
- It's a miracle!
- Miracle!
- Praise the Lord! Hallelujah!
- Hallelujah!
- Adi!
- What happened?
Which of your legs was broken?
The right leg, bhabhi.
- The right leg.
- Okay.
And the plaster is there.
It's really…
What are you doing?
Shit! Shit!
What happened?
This is the one, bro?
Press the bell.
Bro!
Automatic!
- Bro…
- Yeah.
Are you sure this
is bhabhi's house?
Don't know.
I've also come here for the first time.
Aaliya!
Bro, I can't see anything.
- Electricity went off, man.
- Okay.
Aaliya!
Aaliya…
Hey, open the door.
Somebody, please, open the door.
But who closed the door?
The one who opened it
must have closed it.
Don't scare me, bro.
Aaliya!
Aaila!
Who's this Aaila, bro?
- It's Aaliya.
- Yes, yes. Aaliya.
Aaliya bhabhi!
Aaliya!
- Aaliya bhabhi!
- Bro!
Bro!
Bro, no.
No, bro.
Bro!
Are you sure this is bhabhi's house?
Bro, underwear ghost.
Not "underwear" ghost.
It's an undercover ghost.
Yes, exactly.
Are you tired?
Want some tea, brother?
Less sugar, along
with some biscuits, sister.
Right, bro?
- Hey, run! Run!
- Run! Run!
- Aaliya! Aaliya!
- Open the door, please.
Anyone here?
- Open the door! Open the door!
- Please, help us!
Open the door!
Hey…
What happened, bro?
Did you find the way out?
We are done for real.
Let us go.
She's the Burj Khalifa of ghosts.
You wanted to have some tea.
Right, bro?
Elder sister is coming
with the biscuits.
No. No, biscuits. Bread will do.
Sister, you got long hands.
Please, open the latch.
Bro.
She has a hearing problem.
I told her to open the lock,
but she has handed over her head.
No! Run, run, run, run!
Here you go.
Have some tea and biscuits.
Take it, brother.
Take it.
Okay, sister.
Run!
- Tea and biscuits.
- Sorry…
- Let's run away.
- Bro…
- Come on, bro!
- Run! Quick!
- Run…
- Bro, come fast.
We will jump from the terrace. Run, bro!
Bro!
Bro! Bro! Bro!
- Ghost!
- Aaliya!
- Guddu?!
There's a ghost in this house.
Yes! The ghost that serves tea
and sweeps the floor.
You guys are looking like ghosts.
No. There's a ghost in this house.
No one is here except
Gangubai and my kids.
Didn't they meet you?
Kids.
Hide it. Hurry up.
Kids?
- Hurry up, kids. Your mom is calling you.
- Yes.
Dad, whether it's Guddu or anyone else,
no one can ever replace you.
No one.
Go freshen up.
I'll send the kids to you.
But remember,
you've got to impress them, okay?
Kids!
- Namaste!
Bro… they're so well-behaved!
Not well-behaved.
These kids are a menace.
They had set up the horror treatment.
Really?
Aren't you ashamed?
You turned your soon-to-be pop
into popcorn?
But why did you do
this surgical strike on us?
Because a third-class person like you,
who deals in second-class things,
can never be a part of
our first-class mother's life.
You can never replace
our dad in our lives.
Never.
Your dad's place is up there on the wall.
I'd never want to take that place.
I'll carve out my own place in this house.
Juice.
Do you want to make
your own place in this house?
So, shall we start discussing
your marriage with Gangubai?
Hey!
What am I going to do with this trash?
- No way. Get lost.
- Gangu ji…
what do you think about me?
Hey, idiot!
I rejected Ajay Devgn,
and you think I'd choose Sanjay Mishra?
Get lost!
Look, even she's not ready.
Here come the snacks!
Come, let's eat.
- Excuse me, please.
- It's important.
How's he?
What?!
Prithvi is coming
to Chamboli Ghat on Sunday?
Is the information correct?
Okay.
Kids?
Guddu, I think we need
to give some more time to the kids.
Let's go on a bonding trip this Sunday?
Sunday?!
He has to go to Chamboli Ghat
on Sunday. It's important.
So, let us join you guys.
You can finish your work,
and we will have a bonding trip too.
- But…
- Guddu, please.
We have to go.
Guddu!
He's very kind at heart.
Okay.
Ever since I fell in love with you
I've started forgetting
My name and identity
It's only you, I search for everywhere
Restlessly, I keep circling around you
I've lost my heart, lost myself
And left the whole world behind for you
Your graceful walk has driven me crazy
In the pink saree
With those rosy red cheeks
I look breath-taking
Take my picture, dear
You look absolutely stunning
In the pink saree
O beauty, come take a photo with me
Money, money, money, money
My love, listen to me
I'm yearning for you
There's a storm raging wildly
Inside my heart
I've lost my sleep and senses
The moment you came close to me
I wish to propose you once again
No one in this world feels
As beautiful as you
I want this story of ours
To go on forever
You shine fresh and warm
Just like morning sunlight
Come, let's take a flight
Somewhere far away
Don't ignore me, my love
Or else I'll die
In the pink saree
With those rosy red cheeks
I look breath-taking
Take my picture, dear
You look absolutely stunning
In the pink saree
O beauty, come take
A photo with me
Money, money, money, money
Hey, Paro.
We should get married now.
For that, you need
to talk to my dad.
Shut up!
I know these rich people very well.
We will first get married
and then meet your dad.
You forgot to take this flower.
Stop blushing, Paro.
Lallan, she's the d…
D…
Keep the palanquin ready!
I'm going to get married.
He's going to get cheated on for sure.
Bride and groom, exchange the garlands.
Hurry up. Come.
Bride and groom, get your picture taken.
Get it clicked properly.
Seth!
Where are you? Come out!
Look here.
Your son-in-law has come home.
Come, Seth. Come.
- Congratulations, Seth.
- To you, too.
What are you whispering
in each other's ears?
- Son, I was saying that--
- I know what you are going to say.
You might want to tell me
that I should leave Paro.
And in return, you will give me
a blank check. Right?
No, why would I do that?
So, will you give a direct bank
transfer or UPI?
Or NEFT?
You might have an objection
to our marriage,
but let me tell you one thing.
I will never leave Paro.
Never.
Son, no one has any objection
to your marriage.
Look at Paro's dad.
He's so happy.
Look at him.
Dad?!
- Bless you, son!
- Yes.
But Paro is Seth G's daughter.
Yes.
And you're Seth G.
Yes, I'm also Seth G.
What does that mean?
- I mean…
- I'm also Seth G.
So, she has two fathers?
No.
- Both of us are Seth.
- Yes.
What?
- I'm Seth G.
- Okay.
Seth Garibdas.
The owner of this bungalow.
And…
I am G Seth.
Gopaldas Seth.
Driver of this bungalow's owner.
Yes, he's my dad.
Your father-in-law.
- Gopal Seth, the driver.
- Yes.
No!
Son, what are you doing?
- I'm going to kill you.
- But why?
Because of people like you,
people like me lose faith in true love.
No, son.
Who will die first?
Seth G or G Seth?
Seth G!
Okay, Seth G.
Now, G Seth.
- Dad!
- Paro!
What happened to you?
Are you alright?
Was it a dream?
He is too excited.
Yes.
- Rekha, dear.
- Yes.
Bring the welcome platter.
Right away.
Welcome the newly
married couple, dear.
Who's she?
She's my daughter, Rekha.
- She's also of marriageable age.
- Yes.
If you know any suitable guy for her,
even if he's poor like you,
do let me know.
- Don't you go to the temple?
- No.
But today I will definitely go.
So that I can also get
a husband like you.
Let's go, sister.
Today we will cook pumpkin curry.
With puris.
- Some kheer as well.
- Had you come two days earlier,
you would have been my wife.
Such an ill-fated person I am!
Lallan!
I used to tell you from day one.
That she's the d…
What?
Today, you complete
your sentence. Come on.
That's what I was telling you.
She's the d…
driver's daughter!
Yes.
I will kill you, idiot.
"Driver's daughter."
Why didn't you say that earlier?
You were stuck at "d…"
Couldn't you complete
the sentence once?
I could have understood. But you…
No…
No, Lallan. No!
Lallan! Lallan! No…
Boss, who made your boat sink?
- And what's wrong with your walk?
- Forget about my walking style.
Find Prithvi.
I want Prithvi.
Find him from any part of the world.
I want the treasure.
I want the treasure! Go!
Yes, boss.
- Hi!
- Hello!
Where's your bag?
- I'm not coming with you.
- Why?
The kids wanted to go on
a bonding trip with you alone.
And I said okay.
Oh no, I forgot to bring
snacks for the kids.
Wait a minute. Coming.
Guddu.
Snacks!
Snacks.
- Bye. See you.
- Bye.
- Bye. Bye.
- Bye!
- Bye, Mom.
Johnny, get ready fast.
- I'm coming to pick you up.
- Yeah, bro.
God, just for 50 rupees!
You completely ruined my life
just for 50 rupees!
You've given me such
a huge punishment.
Such a huge one!
Today, I managed to make her sleep
by giving her sleeping pills.
But for how long will I be able
to protect my dignity?
Give me another life, God!
I've already ruined this life!
I'm coming to you now!
I'm coming to you.
I'm coming.
I'm coming to you now.
Right now.
What are you doing, son?
Suicide.
Let it be. Do it later.
Take this first.
What's this?
- A gift!
- Gift?
I had bought a plot for Paro.
Near Bhusawal Highway.
You can transfer it to your name.
At what price did you buy it?
- Twenty…
- Lakh?
- Thousands.
- Damn!
Did you buy a plot or a music system?
I'm coming, God.
Son, I bought that plot
20 years ago.
Its present value is approximately
50 lakh rupees.
- How much?
- 50 lakh.
- 50 lakh?
- Yes.
Why are you doing that?
- My luck has turned away from me.
- What?
I consumed this rat poison.
Why didn't you tell me that earlier?
Stupid.
Haven't you tasted
rat poison ever in your life?
Can't you recognize the taste?
It's rose water.
Rose water?!
- What kind of system is this?
- What?
The rich man's name is Garibdas.
- Driver's name is Seth G.
- Right.
This rat poison bottle
is filled with rose water.
What do you fill
the rose water bottle with?
- Kerosene.
- Kerosene!
What kind of a system is that?
Leave that. Come with me.
I've bought a three-wheeler for you.
- What?
- And this is the key.
There's your auto.
- Auto?
- Yeah.
Is this an auto-rickshaw key
or a rocket key?
You fool!
Rocket doesn't require any key.
It only needs a matchstick.
Just light it, and there you go.
This is the real key.
Go in the auto.
Okay. You drink this.
Papers.
Hey, son-in-law.
What's it?
Take Paro along.
Her thumbprint will be required
for the transfer.
What if I take her thumb only?
I was just joking. Hey, Paro.
Wake up fast. You're fast asleep.
- He's too funny.
- Wake up now.
- But he takes good care of Paro.
- You're fast asleep.
Three bags are kept.
Whatever!
Oh shit!
Why won't it close?
Hey!
- It's not…
- Manav, what are you doing?
Your bhabhi is half inside
and half outside.
- Sorry.
- Please come.
- Sorry, bhabhi. Sorry.
- Go, sit in the car.
Okay.
Are you alright?
Adi, enough.
You've got time till you drop me home.
Before this trip ends,
you will have to decide
who you want to live with.
With your brother Manav or with me.
Otherwise, my lawyer will see you
with the divorce papers.
- Rosy, divorce…
- Let's go.
Aarav, how strange!
You get momo on the highway, too.
Bro, because of these kids,
this is the sixth time
we are having tea.
Mark my words,
we are not on a journey.
Rather, we are suffering.
Buffering without a network.
And these kids.
They made us halt a lot of times.
A three-hour-long drive
has turned into a marathon.
They are forced on us.
- We must entertain them.
- Yeah.
Kids.
If you want to eat anything else,
don't hesitate.
Yes!
We are a family.
Of course.
We'll put him in such a condition
that from Monday to Sunday,
he'll be scared of just one thing.
Family.
This fatso stuffs a lot.
These days, he's dieting.
- Okay.
- Anyway, leave that.
I will drop you and the kids at the hotel
and grab Prithvi first.
Then we will deal with these kids.
Prithvi!
No, bro. I'm Johnny.
Look there. Prithvi!
Bro…
- Hey, stop.
- What happened to them all of a sudden?
Maybe nature's call.
Hey, leave him. Leave him.
- Leave!
- Leave me.
Guddu, you?!
I'm alive, you moron.
But now, you will not be spared.
Jagga, has the boss appointed a new man?
Who's that?
Who's he beating up?
Brother, you can beat me up later.
But save me from these goons first.
Come, I will break your skull.
Hey, no. Don't hit me here.
The map is fixed in my memory.
If you hit there,
the map might get deleted.
Bloody…
Run!
Guddu, let's quickly go away, please.
- Guddu!
- Bro!
Kids, for God's sake, give us the key.
Please.
Get lost.
Do not touch my kids.
Oh no!
Hey, catch those kids.
Get in. Quick!
Where has Prithvi gone?
Boss, somebody took him away
in a car.
In a car?
Who took him away in a car?
Boss, he must be Guddu.
Guddu, that rascal. Guddu!
Guddu, you wanted us
to get killed by those goons?
I see. As if you wanted
to get me rewarded today.
Your kids are too sweet.
Forget the kids, talk to the elders.
Tell me, where is
Shaitan Singh's treasure? Tell me!
You said you've memorized the map.
So, tell me where it is now.
Shaitan Singh's treasure?!
History chapter six.
The Hidden Pirate Treasure.
Do you know the secret
to Shaitan Singh's treasure?
Keep quiet, both of you.
You tell me now.
- Telling you.
- Tell me now.
Guddu, don't leave him.
- Uncle, hold him.
- Hold him.
Hold him tight.
- Johnny, hold him.
- I'm holding him.
- Hey…
- Hold him, please.
Tell me quickly. Where's the treasure?
Don't let go!
Look ahead!
Where are we going, bro?
Down in the ravine.
- Where has he gone?
- Where's Prithvi?
Oh, shit, bro!
He really went down to earth, bro!
If someone falls from this cliff,
even God can't save him.
We lost the treasure
because of you, Guddu.
You're a complete failure.
Hey, you both are responsible for this.
Hey. Stop shouting at us.
It's not our mistake.
It's not your mistake?
Both of you are a mistake!
I wonder what came to my mind
that I thought of being your dad.
- I wish to throw you…
- Hey!
- His weight is too much.
- Help!
Hey, I just threatened you.
Why are you shouting?
I didn't throw you for real.
Somebody, please help.
Over here.
- Bro!
- That hand!
Help!
Help! Please!
Bro, Prithvi. Prithvi is alive.
Prithvi is alive.
- Prithvi is alive!
- Prithvi is safe!
- Our treasure is safe.
Our treasure?
Yes, of course.
- We are a family, right?
- Yes. Family.
Family.
Before the property gets divided,
you'd better reduce the family size.
Throw them down.
- Why? Who do you think you are?
- Help!
- Help! Help!
Guddu, save him first.
Yes.
You're a champ, Guddu.
- Yes, Guddu. You can do it.
- You can do it.
- Come on, Guddu!
Stop it.
Let him concentrate.
Yes, you can do it, Guddu.
Guddu, you can do it.
Come on, Guddu!
You can do it.
- You can do it.
- Concentrate, bro.
You can do it, Guddu.
- Ram, Ram, Ram, Ram.
- Yes, you can do it.
It's a matter of treasure.
Please, Guddu.
- Ram, Ram, Ram, Ram.
- Yes, you can do it. You can do it.
- Ram, Ram, Ram.
- Yes, you can do it.
- You can do it.
- Ram, Ram, Ram.
- Guddu, be careful!
- Ram! Ram! Ram!
- I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead.
- You can do it.
Guddu! Guddu, careful!
Oh no!
What happened, Guddu?
Johnny, do something.
Save me.
- God!
- Bro, I'm there.
I will teach you how to walk
on such a slippery surface.
Just now.
- Watch me, okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
- All the best!
- What?
All the best!
Johnny!
- Yes.
- You can do it, Uncle.
- You can do it.
- Coming.
- Yes.
- Uncle.
- Coming.
- Oh no, Uncle.
- Be careful, Uncle.
- Look here. Place your right leg first…
- Be careful.
- Then take your left leg…
- Uncle, be careful!
- Then the right… and then left…
- Be careful!
Even this idiot has slipped.
Have you come to rescue me
or kill me?
Bro, this life is meaningless
without you. I love you.
Get lost.
Guddu, are you okay?
I'm okay so far.
But it won't be the same
for a long time.
Go and seek help.
- Yes, we're going.
- Yes, we will. Come, Aarav.
Help!
Keep the plot's documents properly.
- Yes.
- Stop! Stop!
- Help! Help!
- Help!
How did these kids come here?
- Oh no!
- Look in the front.
- Help! Help!
- I'm here.
Because you're there, I need help.
Go back.
- Adi! Adi, accident!
- Are you alright?
You should be in school.
What are you doing here?
- Do you wish to die?
- We need help!
No! We need help…
My auto's seat is broken.
Moreover, she fell on me.
I was almost dead.
You should have thought about your
auto before taking the passenger.
He's not an auto driver.
- He's my husband.
- You need not give the details.
- But…
- Who will pay for the damage?
You've willingly married her.
Why should we pay for the damage?
Hey, you…
He knows the secret to the treasure.
Pay for the damage!
Can you please repeat that?
He knows the location
of Shaitan Singh's treasure.
I know about this.
It's a 100-year-old treasure.
Shaitan Singh's treasure!
Yes.
There's something called humanity.
I will save the treasure.
I mean the man who needs help.
Where's he hanging?
- That side.
- Bring a rope. Quick. Manav.
- Adi, every time we've run after money,
- What?
- we've ended up getting in problems.
- Zip it!
- Adi, thrice…
- Keep quiet.
- Adi, we end up with nothing.
- Quiet. Bring a rope.
- Where?
- Okay.
- They're there.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
Come on.
- Let's go and find the treasure.
- Come fast.
Oh no. This is dangerous.
Over there.
Don't worry.
We will rescue you.
Yes, we will rescue you as well
as the secret to the treasure.
You told them about the treasure?
We had to tell them
before they agreed to help!
Now, quickly tell us
the secret to the treasure.
Then we will rescue you.
Between the two of you,
who knows the secret to the treasure?
You idiots!
Only I know the secret to the treasure.
Hurry up and rescue me.
Who said that?
Your dad, the one who's hanging.
My dad hanged himself from the fan.
Where is he hanging?
Leave that.
Tell us clearly,
who do we have to rescue?
The two of you?
Or the one who's hanging?
Rescue all three of us.
Hey, oldie.
The other guy who's hanging
knows the secret.
Why should we rescue you?
Hurry up, man. Please.
Stop the discussion.
Rescue all of them.
Manav, throw that rope.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Idiot, what have you done?
What have you done?
You've thrown the rope
into the valley?
You told me to throw the rope,
which I did.
Don't waste time, man.
Hurry up. Help!
How do we save them now?
I've got an idea.
Let's hold each other's hands
and make a human chain.
- Okay.
- Fine, who would lead the human chain?
Come forward!
Uncle, you're the bravest of all.
Me? Brave? How?
That's why you came forward.
No, I didn't.
I don't know how,
but every time there's danger,
I somehow end up stepping
forward first.
Adi!
Help! Please, hurry up.
But where are you?
Where are you?
Go ahead and check.
Don't let go of the hand.
Hold each other's hands.
Hold each other's hands tightly.
Listen, extend your hand.
Extend your hand.
Very good!
Come on. Keep holding my hands.
Please, do something.
Give your hand. Come on.
Okay… don't move now.
Don't worry.
I'm holding this tree.
The tree won't run away.
Hold me tightly.
Stand straight, all of you.
I will try to reach him.
Yes. Bro, concentrate.
Concentrate!
- Bro, concentrate.
- Bend, guys. Bend a little.
- Bend a little more.
- Concentrate!
- Bend more.
- Concentrate.
- Enough. We're bending too much.
Come on.
Come. Come.
- Come on.
- Be careful!
Come down a little.
Why are they going in reverse?
Who's dragging everyone?
- Oh no!
- Guddu, please don't do that.
Very good!
Yes! Yes!
Yes, Guddu! Very good!
Very good, Guddu!
Be careful! Come!
- Come. Come.
- Come down a little. Come.
The cliff has become an escalator.
Oh no!
Hey, Guddu!
- Guddu!
- Prithvi.
- Guddu.
- Yes?
I'm losing my grip!
I'm going straight out in one shot!
Guddu, I'm gone.
Don't be scared! I'll pull you up.
- Wait!
- Guddu!
I betrayed you so many times,
yet every single time,
you saved me. But now…
I won't survive.
This is the punishment for my greed.
Hey, stop this emotional drama!
Tell us the secret of the treasure.
And tell him to say the location
of the treasure loudly.
- Otherwise, my hand will slip.
- Hey!
Speak louder! Louder! Come on.
Janakpur Jetty is 50 kilometers from here.
From there, 120 kilometers south
into the sea,
there's an island.
An island.
What's the name?
Prithvi Deshpande!
What do we do with your name?
Tell us the name of that island.
The island does not have any name.
How do I search on Google Maps?
Come on, it must have a name.
Do you want to make
an identity card for that island?
Please, continue.
You will easily identify that island.
There's a giant "M" on the island.
A giant "M".
- "M."
- "M" for mother?
Yes.
"M" for Mother.
Adi, I miss Mom.
This is not the time, Manav!
But how do we identify that giant "M"?
That giant "M" is made out of mountains.
You'll be able to spot it from far away.
But to reach that "M",
you'll have to pass through
a dense and dangerous jungle!
Tell us,
where will we find the treasure
once we reach that giant "M"?
Yes, please clarify that.
The treasure is beneath that giant "M",
behind an "O".
- Behind what?
- Behind an "O"?
Beneath the "M",
behind an "O".
- He's gone.
- Hey, Adi.
He's gone.
Adi, even he is gone.
- Who?
- The one who held my hand.
Hold him. Hold him.
- We are safe. We are safe.
- Guddu…
We are safe. We are safe.
It feels like death
itself is coming for us.
Hey, snail, crawl up.
Manav, pull up.
Adi, we will die.
Don't worry. Cheaters like us
don't die so easily.
Keep moving. Carefully.
Come on. Carefully.
- Come on. Come on, Manav.
- Yes. Come.
What was that?
What's happening?
- Adi…
- Come on, Manav.
Manav, crawl up fast.
Hurry up.
I am trying, Adi. I am trying.
Pull up, Manav.
- Crawl up, man.
- Hurry up.
Come on up.
Hurry up. Come on.
- Hurry up.
- Come on, Manav. Come on.
Come on. We're almost there.
Hey…
Sorry, bro.
- Sorry for what, bro?
- For this.
Hey, Uncle Johnny!
- He said sorry, then kicked me, bro!
- Adi!
- Uncle, this is cheating.
- Adi, let's go.
- This is cheating!
- I like to cheat! I like to cheat!
- Let's go, Manav.
- Uncle, this is cheating.
Johnny!
- Come on, Johnny. Crawl up.
- Try it to climb up.
- Yes, crawl up. Try.
- Yes, try to crawl up.
- Crawl.
- Yes, very good.
- Good! Very good!
- Don't give up. Very good.
- Careful!
- Be careful!
I got hold of the branch, bro!
- Come up.
- Come on.
I hope this tree won't get uprooted.
- Oh, no! Come with me!
- Oh, no!
Don't let go, Johnny! Hang on!
Bro, keep holding tight!
Wait. Hold on tight.
- Bro!
- Don't let go!
- Johnny!
- I won't!
Nala and Neela built the Ram Setu bridge.
- You make me your bridge. Bro.
- I'm coming.
- Hold on tight.
- Don't worry, bro.
No, I can't…
Wait, Johnny.
Don't let go, Johnny.
Johnny, don't let go.
Don't let go.
Pull me up, bro.
Hold on. Let me catch my breath.
Johnny, wait and see.
No one can take the treasure except me.
Shut up! I'll take the treasure!
Paro, hop in! Quick!
We'll fly to the treasure.
Yes, I'm coming.
Is it fine?
It's really windy, Paro.
Hey, my hot-air balloon!
My hot-air balloon!
Bye-bye!
We will return it to you soon!
My hot-air balloon!
Will you turn this bicycle into
an airplane to catch us?
Look in the front.
See, you caused an accident.
Goodbye! Enjoy the fish fry!
Listen,
we shouldn't have
left them to die.
Nothing will happen to them.
All of them are cheaters.
They must have managed to crawl up
and must be chasing us.
You weren't in Total Dhamaal, right?
But I was there.
Stop thinking about them.
Enjoy this scenery.
Hey, look there.
Such a beautiful Indra Kumar.
Well, it's "Indra Dhanush".
Whatever it is.
Both are exceptional.
Someday I will tell you their stories.
Listen to this story right away.
At the time of shooting…
My boat.
Adi, that fatso is running after us.
I won't let you go.
Oh no!
He fell into the water.
I don't know him.
Leave it. Look in the front.
Okay.
Adi! That bearded beggar left us
and ran away.
Bloody basket! Cheater cock.
He was quite cunning.
If I find him, I won't spare him.
Yes, Adi.
Bro, what have you done?
Hey, my boat. My boat.
- Yeah…
- Bro.
Were these greedy idiots the only people
you could find to ask for help?
Those fellows ran away, leaving
us to die!
But they looked decent
and innocent to us!
How can you tell if someone
is decent just by his face?
Just look at bro!
- Hey, you…
- I am sorry.
- Control the boat.
- Bro…
Bro! Bro!
I won't spare those people.
Hey, first pick up some speed.
- Yeah, speed up, Guddu!
- Speed up.
Paro, you may have played
with the balloons in childhood.
But did you ever imagine
that one day you would fly
in a hot air balloon?
Never imagined it…
But this is so much fun!
When we find the treasure,
it'll be even more fun.
How much do you eat?
Your stomach is rumbling so loudly!
My stomach isn't upset.
Look over there.
Your stomach will get upset.
Not just the stomach.
Pants will get ruined, too.
Once we get our hands
on this treasure,
we'll become billionaires very soon!
According to that, how much
is my share, bhabhi?
Simple, Manav.
One share yours, one mine,
and one will be of your bhabhi's.
Not so simple.
There will only be two shares
of the treasure.
Okay? One share is ours,
and one share is ours.
One share for me,
and one share for you two together.
How does that make sense?!
Two of you are one unit, right?
Yeah, Adi! Actually, we've been
brothers since childhood. Right?
Get lost.
"Brothers"!
Look there.
Over there.
Oh no! Adi,
it seems the God of death
has found us again.
Mom, we are coming. Adi…
Guddu, if we find
Shaitaan Singh's treasure,
how rich will we become?
So rich that every Christmas,
you'll be giving gifts to Santa Claus!
I'm going to go shopping
every single day!
And what will you do,
Uncle Johnny?
Nothing. I'll find a nice match
and get married, bro.
Johnny dear,
at your age, not marriage proposals,
but angels come.
And that too, to take you
away with them.
Bro… who's going to save us
from this angel of death, bro?
What do we do, Uncle?
Help!
Mom!
What's happening?
Oh, God!
Please, save us this time.
I promise,
if we survive this storm,
I'll offer you 500 kilos of sweets.
- We survived! We survived!
- We survived.
Now, just remember to offer God
those sweets worth 150,000 rupees.
How 150,000?
You said 500 kilos.
At 300 rupees per kilo,
it will be 150,000 rupees'
worth of sweets, right?
You heard me wrong.
I didn't say 500 kilos,
I said 500 grams. 500 grams.
Why do you turn away
from your promise to God?
How do you know that?
I wasn't a part of Total Dhamaal.
But I had watched it.
Fire! There's a fire.
We're going to die.
No! I won't let anything
happen to my husband.
You cannot die.
Hail Bajrangbali!
Oh, my husband!
Where are you going,
leaving me behind?
I'm leaving the whole world behind.
See you in the next life now.
Goodbye.
Thank God,
I have no motion sickness.
- Adi.
- Yes.
Looks like Lord Yamaraj
has sent his entire army after us.
- Yes, Manav.
- I told you
not to take a boat named Titanic.
It'll sink. We're all going to die.
None of you will die.
Because I will save everyone.
Oh no!
Octopus!
Manav, hit the octopus.
Hit it.
Break his legs.
Oh shit!
Where's the octopus?
Bloody basket!
Attacked my bhabhi?
I'll smash your head.
No… no… no…
Don't hit it.
Pull it off!
Okay, okay…
Leave.
Let go, you bald idiot.
I'll turn you into salad.
Come out.
Leave my bhabhi if you love your life.
Leave her. Let go.
I said let go.
Hey! Hey, what are you doing?!
I'm drowning it to death.
Who are you drowning to death?!
The octopus.
Idiot! Your bhabhi will die.
Bhabhi will die?
- Take her out.
- Oh shit!
What are you doing?
- You will kill your bhabhi.
- I am sorry, Adi.
Adi, this thing is attacking with
the whole family.
This storm doesn't seem to stop.
Don't panic!
This storm will stop soon.
What happened, bro?
The storm didn’t stop, but the boat did.
I'm not getting down to push it.
I’m a senior citizen, bro.
Hey, a while ago you were talking
about getting married.
Now, suddenly you became
a senior citizen?
Wait! I'll check.
- Yeah! Check.
- Hey, leave me first.
Check.
Concentrate, bro. Hold this.
- Start!
- Guddu!
- Guddu! Bro.
Help me!
- Stop the boat! I'm drowning.
- Guddu! Do something, Uncle.
Hey, Johnny! Johnny, stop the boat.
Johnny! Johnny, stop the boat.
Okay.
Hey, what are you doing?!
Which button did you press?
The red one.
You weren't supposed to press that.
Oh shit!
I forgot Dhamaal 1, bro.
Phone! Phone!
Phone… Aala… Aala…
Aaliya! Aaliya! Aaliya!
Guddu, where are you?
What are these strong winds
and this storm-like noise?
Oh… we… we're watching a movie.
"Life Trapped in a Storm."
Oh, okay.
I hope everything is going smoothly.
As smooth as water.
Okay, please let me talk to the kids.
Yes, just hold on.
Hey, phone… Phone…
Hello, Mom.
Hello, dear. Are you
enjoying yourselves?
Yes, we're watching a very good movie.
Oh, very good!
Bhabhi… hang up now.
Otherwise, the hero will die.
I mean… the hero is dying.
Good night, bhabhi. Good night!
Hang up.
Uncle!
What happened?
Looks like the hero isn't dying.
He has actually died.
A shark pulled him away.
Oh shit, Guddu bro.
Even you left us stranded in the middle.
People leave property
behind after their death,
but you left this cheap
jacket behind, bro.
My fate itself is cheap.
Hey, what's that?
Guddu bro,
is it your whole body
or just your head?
Hey, Guddu is following us
like the Sarkata monster.
Wow, Guddu bro! Riding a dolphin.
Bro, people usually
aim for a fish's eye.
But you rode on the fish.
Watch out for the pole.
Fool!
And the thorns!
Paro!
Open your eyes.
Hey!
Hey, look there.
I can see a giant "W".
"W?!"
We've gone so far in reverse that
we've reached the first Dhamaal again.
Good, at least we'll get ten crores.
Hey… this "W" is upside down.
This is an "M".
"M"!
We'll have to do something.
Knife?
Quickly, get up, Paro.
Get up! Come on.
Get up!
Look there.
Look there, Paro.
It's a giant "M".
Come on, Guddu, how many more thorns
are you going to get removed?
Yes, let's go, Guddu.
Have you pulled out all the thorns?
Bro.
Just sit in the water once.
Let me check all the punctures.
- Yeah.
- Shameless.
Bro is in this condition
because of you two.
You've come here for the treasure.
Yes, because we want
a lot of money for our mom.
I would have brought
the treasure for your mom.
Yes, but then you too
would have come along.
We don't want you.
Found it. Found it.
- What did you find now?
- What did you find?
"M".
- "M". Let's go. Come on.
- Damn!
Come on. Let's go.
Adi! Adi!
Adi, bhabhi…
Bhabhi…
Adi! Adi!
Adi!
- Adi!
- What happened?
Adi, Bhabhi…
Half bhabhi?
Where's the other half of bhabhi?
Bhabhi has left us.
- What did you do, Manav?
- Adi, please…
What did you do this time
that she ran away again?
Adi, I didn't do anything.
It's God's doing.
Today, you've
actually become a widower.
Look there.
Hey, Rosy!
- Rosy!
- Bhabhi!
Rosy, why did you leave me alone?
I love you, Rosy.
How will I live without you?
Aren't you dead?
Do you want me to die?
- No! No. I don't want that.
- How can you even think about that?
I won't spare you easily.
What do you think you are?
- I don't need your "sorry."
- Oh, shit!
- I will hit you. You deserve that.
- Adi.
Adi… Bhabhi…
- I won't spare you.
- Adi! Bhabhi…
Shut up!
- "M".
- 'M'.
- Yes.
- "M".
- Let's go.
Stop.
Let us go, man.
We came here by mistake.
Please, spare us.
No… No… No…
- No… No… No… please.
- No… No…
We are safe.
Thank you very much
for sparing our lives.
Bless me, Uncle. Bye.
Let's go.
Stop.
What's it now?
Do not go.
My man…
you fight…
What is he saying?
If you remain alive…
you can go…
Are you a human or a pirated CD?
Getting stuck on every dialogue.
I think he's telling you
to fight with his man.
And if you win, we can go.
Who should I fight with?
Who's this Hu Ha?
Hu Ha, who?
Who is Hu Ha?
Paro, you take the treasure and enjoy.
I'm about to get finished here.
Chiku, you…
Both of you, fight.
- Chiku?
Is he already standing
or yet to stand up?
Will this short fellow fight with me?
You look more like a grape
than a chiku!
You can't even pluck
a mango from a tree.
Will you break my bones?
Hey, Paro, now we will take
the treasure and go together.
I will deal with him right away.
Go… Go…
Why do you bite like a dog?
Leave me.
What are you doing?
One moment.
Look up. Your mother.
Paro!
You're thinking about
seven lifetimes together…
This guy is going to kill me
for fourteen lifetimes, man!
I will never have kids.
You better remarry. Paro.
Where did that destroyer
of my family line go?
I'll send him to his maker!
Paro, give me a spear.
- Quickly!
- Spear…
Found it.
Come on, give it to me.
What kind of a woman are you?
You're practically
making yourself a widow.
Not even one of my legs is left intact.
Chiku!
No… No… No…
Paro…
Chiku!
Paro?!
Attention everyone.
If you beat up my husband…
your clan will be blown away.
None of you
will stay alive.
Understood?
We apologize!
No. No apology.
If my husband forgives you all,
only then will I forgive you.
We apologize.
- We apologize.
- Leave my legs, please.
It's already wounded.
Let's look ahead.
Why did you all stop?
He's asking something.
Tell him.
We are scared.
What if any wild animal appears?
Your general knowledge is very weak.
Wild animals don't live on the islands.
Hey, who is it?
They do.
- They do.
- Yes, they do.
This tiger's general
knowledge is very weak as well.
It came on an island. Idiot!
Oh God!
Singham on top
of another Singham!
Don't get into a scuffle with it.
Just run away.
No… No…
Hey, tiger… tiger…
What will you get by hunting me?
There are three more
items on the menu card.
- No.
- The smaller one is very tasty.
Aarav Do Pyaza.
Hey!
Hey, Guddu, have you lost it?
Don't panic.
I've read somewhere.
If you keep looking into a tiger's eye,
it won't attack.
Come on, tiger, look. Look here.
Watch!
Yes… see.
It turned completely docile now.
- Wow!
- Told you my knowledge
about tigers is spot on.
What are you doing?
Bro, this tiger's general
knowledge is absolutely terrible.
It doesn't even know what it really is.
That tiger is going
to give him a disgraceful death!
Bro!
Saw what I did?
I've hit that idiot so hard,
it'll never come back again.
Hey, why are you screaming?
The tiger's gone now, right?
Let's go.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
- Bro is a genius.
- Yeah.
Adi, lizard…
Lizard…
You also must be tired.
Go drink some water.
I'm very thirsty.
Let me fill the bottle.
Okay.
Adi, you did a good thing
by giving water to the lizard.
Mom will be so proud of you.
- What?
- Yeah. Look there.
It was so thin and small.
After drinking water, it became so huge.
That's not a lizard.
That's your bhabhi.
Not her. The one next to her.
Take a look.
Oh shit!
Idiot, that's not a lizard.
That's a crocodile! A crocodile.
Stay quiet.
Adi, that small stone
can't kill the crocodile.
This is for your bhabhi, you idiot.
Okay.
What happened?
Why are you throwing stones?
What?
What is it?
Stay quiet.
Quietly walk backward. Slowly.
Come back slowly. Slowly.
Absolute silence.
Don't make a sound.
Adi, help!
Adi, what do I do?
Poke in its eye!
Hurry up, poke in its eye!
- Okay… okay…
- Do it.
You idiot, poke the crocodile's eye.
Okay… okay…
Hey, statue!
Adi, it's not staying still.
You've got a knife, right? Cut it!
Cut it, come on.
Yes.
Adi!
This won't be enough
to cut the crocodile.
Idiot. Cut the bottle strap.
Come on.
Yes, come on.
Come on, Manav.
Yes.
Oh my!
Adi… Adi…
Adi…
Run, run, run!
"M" is here.
We've reached near "M".
- Let's go.
- Come.
Get down!
Get up.
Guddu, there could be danger inside.
There’s no danger,
there's only treasure inside.
Come on, hold each other's hands
and let's go.
"M". M for money.
M for…
Look there. The way to go inside.
- Let's go.
Adi, there could be danger inside.
Just shut up.
Okay.
Paro, look there.
"M" is here.
Yeah!
Hey.
Look there.
Let's go inside and find
a way to enter "O".
Don't you find this place dangerous?
What's there to be scared of?
Just don't be scared.
Walk closely.
Keep walking.
Adi, this place looks
extremely dangerous.
You think you'll find
Shaitaan Singh's treasure
in a coffee shop?
Found it.
This must be the way
to get into the "O".
- Yes! Yes!
- Come on. Let's go.
Pull it, bhabhi.
It's really quiet here.
Listen, Paro. Don't flirt.
I only let you hold my finger,
and you've already got your whole hand
inside my shirt!
Is this really the time to get romantic?
I didn't do anything.
Really? You didn't do anything?
You didn't do anything, huh?
Then…
what is this?
What is this? Tell me!
You got scared looking at your own hand?
That's not my hand. It's a snake!
It's a snake?
It's a…
It really is a snake.
Why is it flicking its tongue so much?
He turned out to be a Casanova
among snakes.
Listen, buddy, this is a family film.
That stuff doesn't happen here.
- Run! Run! Run!
- Run!
Bro.
Bro, stop.
- It's too dark.
- I'm scared.
My eyes have night vision.
I can see everything.
We survived.
Adi!
- What happened?
- We won't survive!
No… no… Don't move.
Don't move. Don't move.
Don't sneeze. No.
Don't sneeze. Please, no.
Don't sneeze.
Thank you.
Bro, we survived this time as well.
You too have reached?
Bro, he was the one who kicked.
Damn, you…
Oh shit!
Help! Help!
He has been crushed.
- Help!
- I am here.
Because you're here,
I need help. Get up, now.
Yes, yes.
So, you people made it here, too?
Even this traitor showed up.
Beat him up.
- Beat him up.
- Hey…
Don't you dare touch my husband!
I will crush him right here.
Madam, you don't know us.
We are the dangerous villains.
Right, Bro?
You look more like a comedian.
With one tight slap,
you will start saying,
"Sister, I've never
seen someone like you."
Listen, we don't raise our
hands on women. Understand?
But I do raise my hand on men.
Come on. Come forward.
Adi, woman power.
Don't mess.
Stop fighting and look for the "O".
Good idea. Let's look
for the "O". Where's it?
- "O".
- Yes, Bro, "O".
- Find the "O".
- Where's the "O"?
- Where's "O"?
- Look there.
Where?
Those are the skeletons.
Does that mean people were
trapped and have died even here?
That means we will also die
and get trapped here, Adi.
Guddu! We don't want to die.
Please, save us.
- Save me this time, Bro.
- Leave me.
Wait!
Seems so.
There's no way out of this place.
Damn, this Shaitan Singh!
Guddu!
Is your hand hollow?
It’s sounding hollow.
Idiot, this wall is hollow.
If the wall is hollow,
let's break it.
Stone! Stone!
Yes, pick up the stone.
Let's break it with stones.
Bro!
The treasure, Bro!
Oh, damn!
The treasure!
- Let's get it, bro.
- Treasure.
We found the treasure!
Let's go. Let's go.
- The treasure.
- Come on. Manav, let's grab it.
Come on. Come on.
- Treasure.
- Here. Here.
So much money!
So much treasure!
Let me grab it.
We are the richest people now.
Hereafter, my name is Johnny Gates.
Manav, Rosy, find the diamonds.
Diamonds. Diamonds.
Hey, this is more
precious than the Kohinoor.
We will dip these
biscuits in milk and eat.
What are you waiting for?
- Grab as much as you can.
- Yes.
- Take these as well.
- Chocolate, PS5, pizza, we'll buy it all.
Now, we've become wealthy.
Mom won't have to work anymore.
Grab as much as you can.
Everything is for your mom.
God! If only we could get a sack now.
Excuse me!
A sack.
A girl by your side,
and a sack in your hand.
You got lucky.
- Thank you. Open the sack.
- Yes, yes.
Hurry up.
- Bhabhi, a sack.
- Thank you.
May the evil eyes stay away.
Santa Claus uncle, take this.
Thank you, lollipop.
From where did you get this sack?
That uncle gave me.
Hello, friends.
- Adhoora, you?!
- "Adhoora?"
But he seems complete.
Adhoora is back.
Grab it… grab the treasure for me.
Come on. Come on.
Why should we grab it out for you?
And who are you, crooked walker?
A finance minister?
No. A defense minister.
- Pirates, the gunner.
- Bro…
Adhoora, how did you reach here?
Am I putting on a show?
Why are you all clapping?
Hey, come out.
Prithvi, you?!
Prithvi Deshpande?!
Is he alive?
This is cheating.
Every time the one who tells
the secret to the treasure dies.
The same thing happened
in the last three parts.
How did you survive?
I'll tell you.
Behind the "O".
Gun shooter G9.
- Hello!
- Get lost!
Alright, enough of your story now.
Go stand in line with the others.
- How come?
- Do as I say.
But I'm on your team now.
I brought you all here.
Oh really?
Now, I will send you up
to the other world. Go there.
You cheater. If I get
out of this place alive,
I won't spare you. Hold this.
Thank you.
- Give it back!
- Hey!
Make everyone stand in a line.
- Everyone, stand in a line.
- Hurry up.
- Come on. Come on.
- We're already in line.
- In line. In line, move.
- Come on.
Ready.
They came here to loot the treasure.
Now, whatever items
all of you've grabbed,
- return everything. Jheenga.
- Yes.
- Drop it.
- Come on.
Take that out.
Chocolates are gone.
Pizza is gone.
So is the burger.
Keep it in here.
Take it out.
- Give it.
- I'm sorry. You can go ahead.
Okay. Hey!
Wanted to become rich
but turned into idiots.
Wanted to become billionaires,
instead became beggars.
You filthy fellow, go to hell!
Put it back.
Adi, give back the thing
you've put in your mouth.
No, Adi. No violence.
What is it?
Take it out.
How much time will you take?
Hey…
Take it out. Take it out, quickly.
You will be cursed.
No, I won't be.
We don't use the incense sticks, okay?
Keep this.
- Hey, girl, take everything out.
- Come on. Take it out.
Come on.
- Bhabhi's bangles.
- May you be ruined!
May your children
be born squint-eyed.
- Like this?
- Here you go.
May you never be at peace in life!
- Take this, too.
- Wow!
And what about the one in your wrist?
That's my personal item.
We are professional pirates.
Robbers! Give it.
Give it. Give it. Give it.
Who would dare ask her?
No problem, move ahead.
Hey, hero!
- Come on.
- Give away everything.
Hey, return that.
You seem very clever.
Did you switch the sacks?
What's in your mouth?
Hey, what's in your mouth?
Take it out.
I said take it out.
What is this?
It's betel leaf spit, man.
It's sweet. Want to taste it?
Hey, this guy's crazy.
Completely mad.
He's a psycho. An idiot…
Yes…
All this treasure, Jheenga…
Now, it belongs to me.
We won't let you take
this treasure away!
- Hey.
- We won't let you…
Don't move.
Get ready to die!
Kill all of them!
Gunmen!
Aim!
Fire!
What happened?
How?
Jheenga…
…what happened?
Boss, that ship had sunk
in the water, right?
- Yes.
- So, water got inside the guns.
We didn't have time to repair them.
And we didn't find any
shop on the way, either.
Jheenga, you…
Hey!
Stop! Stop!
This is a very powerful bomb.
- Step back.
- You can't do this.
I will do it.
And I'll do exactly this.
No one can stop me.
- Boss!
- Yes, Jheenga!
Fire!
Of course I'll light it before
throwing the bomb at them.
They'll be blown into pieces.
Boss, we'll die, too.
No way, Jheenga.
I'll throw this bomb over there.
Those idiots will die.
All of us will die.
Look, Jheenga, look how they're
begging for their lives.
Look there.
Boss, we won't even
be left alive to beg.
- Jheenga.
- Yes.
Why do your eyes make it seem
like I've already lit the bomb?
Yes, you did.
You idiot.
Oh no. It's gone.
Everything is gone.
The treasure is gone!
No, no! Don't go there.
- The treasure…
- Adi, the treasure is gone.
Treasure is lost.
Everything is gone.
Bro.
Adhoora!
- Tell me, Jheenga.
- What should I say?
Your father gave you the right name.
Adhoora.
You can never complete any task.
You're bad luck even for yourself.
Why don't you jump into
this pit and die, Adhoora?
Idiot! First you burned the map,
now you've destroyed
the treasure, too.
I won't spare you.
- Run!
This is breaking, bro.
Oh shit.
Mom! Mom!
Move! Move! Run away.
- Bro!
- Run! Move away!
Come on. Come on.
- Run, bro.
- Run, run!
Run!
- Come on!
- Hurry up.
Oh no! Be careful.
Be careful!
Come on, kids!
- Hello, Aaliya.
- Hi, Guddu!
How's your bonding trip going?
- Everything is falling apart.
- Give it to me.
Hello, bhabhi!
The climax is going on right now.
Hang up for now.
Otherwise, along with the hero,
the supporting cast
will die too, bhabhi!
Listen, Johnny…
Careful, Paro!
Let's jump.
- Let's jump across.
- No, no…
I can't do it.
I won't be able to jump. No.
You can do it. Come on, jump.
No, I can't.
Take this.
These are the property documents.
I've already put my thumbprint.
You'll get 50 lakhs.
I know…
…you don't love me.
I'm just a burden on you.
So, go…
Today, I free you from every bond.
Maybe I'm a little greedy man…
…but I'm not a coward
to leave my wife in the
jaws of death and run away.
Now, I'll jump only with you.
No, but…
How will you carry me?
When a person becomes
responsible, Paro,
then no matter how heavy
the responsibility is,
he carries it somehow.
Lord Rama crossed the
ocean to save Goddess Sita.
I also belong to the land of Lord Rama.
So, can't I at least take
this small jump to save you?
Glory to Lord Rama!
We survived!
You survived…
…but I got buried inside.
Come on. Come on.
Come fast. Run!
- Come on.
- Bhabhi!
Rosy, come fast.
Oh shit!
Bhabhi!
Oh shit, Bhabhi!
Manav! Manav, please save me.
Bhabhi, don't panic.
I'll save you.
Don't worry.
I'm there, bhabhi.
Manav, let go of my hand,
or you'll fall, too.
No, bhabhi.
No matter what happens,
I won't let go of your hand.
I won't leave.
Manav, listen to me.
No, bhabhi.
Manav, leave me!
You will also fall.
Leave me.
Mom, please help!
Manav, don't let go of her.
Pull up, Adi.
- Manav, don't let go.
- I won't.
- Come, bro. Come.
- Come on, kids.
Come, bro.
Run faster, kids!
Aarav.
Oh Bro!
- Uncle Johnny!
- Stop!
Uncle Johnny!
Bro!
Uncle Johnny survived!
- Yes, he survived!
- Johnny Uncle!
But how will we survive?
Guddu… now it'll be difficult
for us to survive.
Not until I'm alive!
Guddu, please save us.
Both of you will have to trust me.
- Okay?
- Yes.
Yes.
Close your eyes.
Johnny!
Catch her.
Are you okay?
Thank you!
Bro!
- Come on, quickly.
- No, Guddu, no… No. I'll die.
No, Guddu!
Guddu, please!
- Save me, please.
- Bro!
Help me! Help me!
Guddu, I don't want to die.
Nothing will happen to you.
- Save me.
- Careful!
Come up, son.
- Aarav.
- Bro!
Guddu!
What are you doing?
Come on.
No, Guddu.
No, I can't do this.
- I will die.
- Shut up.
Nothing will happen to you.
Trust me, please.
Please, son.
Come on.
Come, my brave boy.
Get up.
Bro, you also come down now.
Come, Guddu!
Come on!
- Bro!
- Guddu!
Guddu!
- Bro!
- Guddu, careful!
Come on!
- Bro!
- Guddu!
Guddu!
- Are you alright?
- Yes.
I'll lose some weight, okay.
Paro,
you need not lose weight.
I will let go of my greed.
- I'm sorry, Paro.
- What are you doing?
Don't do that.
You're my husband.
You're like my God.
Are you alright?
Thank you, Manav.
Welcome, bhabhi.
Well,
you had told me that
before this trip ends,
I'll have to make a decision.
My decision is that…
I can't live without Manav.
I'm sorry.
Send me the divorce papers.
I'll sign them.
Let's go, Manav.
No, Adi,
if we leave her behind,
Mom won't be proud of us.
Let's go, Manav.
No, Adi, I won't go.
- No.
- Adi!
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I've realized
that family members
don't need to be perfect.
They just need to have
love for each other.
I'm sorry, Manav!
Bhabhi, why are you apologizing?
I should be the one apologizing.
No… What are you doing?
- Get up!
- Hey, man.
Oh shit.
What have you done?
You broke her nose.
What?
It's okay.
Sorry.
- It's okay.
- Sorry. Sorry.
I'll get used to Manav.
See, even bhabhi likes me.
Yes.
Let's go.
Guddu sacrificed his life
to save you two.
Had dad been alive,
he too would've done
the same thing, right?
Sister, our family has
become incomplete again.
Yes, Aarav,
once again we lost our father.
Yes, sister. We lost him.
What if he's still alive?
Who would survive this fall?
He can survive.
Because he's Guddu.
And not any weak fellow.
Guddu!
Guddu, I love you.
Aarav, behave.
Don't call him Guddu.
- Call him dad.
- Yes.
I love you all, too.
The treasure was right in our hands, bro.
And now it's gone.
No… I got two diamonds instead.
- Where?
- Where are they? Show me.
When a person finds his family,
there's no treasure greater than that.
I found these two precious diamonds.
And we also found our hero.
That's you.
So true, Guddu.
I was also blindly running
after the treasure all my life.
I never realized that the
real treasure is with me.
Yes.
The real treasure is always our family.
My bhabhi is back.
Adi is no longer a widower.
Not a widower.
You can say I am still married.
It's the same thing.
Let's quickly go home now.
I want to relish the parathas
made by bhabhi.
- Let's go.
- But how do we go home?
Yes.
Look there.
- That's a ship.
- Yes, a ship.
We'll make it!
We'll make it.
Oh shit!
- What happened?
- We're not safe. We're dead.
Look whose ship it is.
The incomplete man, bro!
Adhoora returns!
Don't be scared.
I'm not a villain anymore.
I've come to understand that
the world loves heroes, not villains.
Guddu saved my life. That's why
I've given up the pirate life.
- That's great.
- Amazing!
I'd heard that Munna Bhai
had given up his gangster life.
This is the first time I've seen
someone give up the pirate life.
- Wow!
- Also…
from now on, this ship is my tourist boat.
You guys are the first ones aboard.
- Wow!
- Good!
Adi, what do I do with this?
Incense? Just throw it out.
Stop!
One more map, bro?
This looks like a map to a huge treasure.
Who's going to decode it?
Hello!
I will do it. Don't worry.
You?!
You are still alive?!
Yeah.
You've escaped death so many times,
you should've died of shame by now!
What do I do?
I just don't feel any shame.
I'll decode it. Yeah.
Come on.
Bring it here.
Oh!
CHATNI
Roll camera and action!
Hey!
Adi, they are shooting something.
How are they shooting without us?
This is our song.
- Yeah, come on.
- Let's go.
They're shooting Dhamaal without us?